(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ありがとう 君がいてくれて 本当よかったよ
Thank you, I'm really glad you were here.
どんな時だって いつも笑っていられる
No matter the time, I can always keep smiling.
例えば 離れていても 何年経っても
Even if we're apart, even if years pass,
ずっと変わらないでしょ
It'll stay the same forever, right?
私たち Best Friend 好きだよ
We're best friends, I love you.
大好きだよ
I love you so much.
こんな遅い時間にゴメンね
Sorry for the late hour.
一人じゃせっぱ詰まってきたの
Being alone, I felt cornered.
君の声 少し聞いたらがんばれる
If I hear your voice just a bit, I can do my best.
なんでも打ち明けられる ママにも言えないことも全部
I can tell you anything, even things I can't tell my mom.
誰よりもわかってくれる
You understand me better than anyone.
嬉しいときには 自分の事みたいに喜んでくれて
When I'm happy, you're glad for me as if it were yourself.
ダメな時はちゃんと叱ってくれる存在
When I'm down, you're the one who scolds me properly.
ありがとう 君がいてくれて 本当よかったよ
Thank you, I'm really glad you were here.
どんな時だって いつも笑っていられる
No matter the time, I can always keep smiling.
例えば 離れていても 何年経っても
Even if we're apart, even if years pass,
ずっと変わらないでしょ
It'll stay the same forever, right?
私たちの Best Friend 好きだよ
We're best friends, I love you.
大好きだよ
I love you so much.
強がってもすぐにバレてる
Even when I bluff, you see right through it.
へこんでる時は真っ先にメールくれる優しさに もう何度も救われて
When I'm depressed, your kindness in emailing me first has saved me many times.
泣きたい時は思いっきり泣けばいい
When I want to cry, you say 'It's okay to cry your heart out,
「そばにいるから」って
because I'm here for you'.
誰よりも強い味方
You're my strongest ally.
そんな君に私は 何かしてあげられているかな？
I wonder if I'm able to do anything for you like that?
何かあったらすぐに飛んでくから 絶対
If anything happens, I'll definitely fly to you right away.
ありがとう 君がいてくれて 本当よかったよ
Thank you, I'm really glad you were here.
どんな時だって いつも笑っていられる
No matter the time, I can always keep smiling.
例えば 離れていても 何年経っても
Even if we're apart, even if years pass,
ずっと変わらないでしょ
It'll stay the same forever, right?
私たち Best Friend 好きだよ
We're best friends, I love you.
大好きだよ
I love you so much.
どんな時でも祈ってるよ
I'm praying for you no matter the time.
世界で一番に幸せになってほしい
I want you to be the happiest person in the world.
ありがとう 君がいてくれて 本当よかったよ
Thank you, I'm really glad you were here.
どんな時だって いつも笑っていられる
No matter the time, I can always keep smiling.
例えば 離れていても 何年経っても
Even if we're apart, even if years pass,
ずっと変わらないでしょ
It'll stay the same forever, right?
私たち Best Friend 好きだよ
We're best friends, I love you.
Ha-ah, ha-ah...
大好きだよ
I love you
Best Friend